So hey guys, I create this amazing tool called SRT generator and
video manager. Basically this tool generates subtitles for
your video by using AI. And the AI sdfsdgsgs sg sdsg shgs s
we are using is AssemblyAI. Okay this is an
amazing AI which will be create your YouTube subtitles
videos sorry subtitles for your videos
in any language by default. Right now I'm in India so basically I'm
using two language which is global English and Hindi. Even you
can add your more language as per your choice. Then you have to put
API for use this tool. Okay once you put
the API you can click on generate and it will give you certain
srt files. So basically these SRT files are called subtitles.
Here you can see in download I have lot of files so you can see
srt okay in english, okay in hindi there are a lot of
Sid files so you can download this once you generate the
Srt file, okay now you have to like test because even
AI can do some kind of mistake like grammatical mistakes and spelling mistakes.
So once you generate the file, okay click on here like
SRT to mp4 and this will be convert your srt file
and mp4 file in sorry MP3 file into mp4 file.
So here you can select MP3 and then you have to select SRt
file and default. Like a lot of time I use, I speak
in Hindi language so I have to use hindi fonts.
Okay so you can select or if you are using the English then you don't
have to worry. And here you have to put the titles, okay like
test or output or final output. You can like put
dot mp4 once you done it. Okay now click on
srt editor. Okay now then english subtitles like
I'm using english subtitles and english subtitle srt and
upload it. Here you can see the video and
you can see clearly this video is totally showing you the
subtitles on a big font. Okay here you can read the
the font. Here you can edit the font as per your choice. Once you add
it you can save it. And if you, if this area is not
look for good for you. Like you need a more area to edit the SRT.
Like here simply you can drag and drop easily
for your choice. This is really easy tool, like easy to manage.
Once you manage everything, okay and you can translate even
your subtitles into various different languages also
like just pick your subtitles by default I used the english subtitles.
Okay so you can translate like in English. Then you can translate in
German, Japanese, French, whatever languages
you want, like even Chinese also. But for Chinese you have to
download again font for Japanese you have download also
fonts. And if you want to download fonts, just click on
download font, upload fonts like dot TTF files
and once you upload it, it definitely download your fonts and you can use
directly this font directly in this tool.
This is an amazing tool once everything is done.
Now there is a twist even if you want to generate some music
for your videos. So here is an open source tool which is
generated 50 seconds music files,
okay. As per your prompt. So you can generate this tool and even
you can use outside audio, video audio files for
your videos, okay. And there's a one important and amazing
concept called YouTube video manager. Here you can manage
your video like ad subtitles, URL's description,
what kind of description or even like you have to manage lot of videos.
Like if once you have like thousands of video, definitely you,
you went out for your old videos, change some videos,
endpoint or ad subtitles, it's totally depend on you.
You can totally manage everything from here and add your videos.
Even you can add it every videos and this is
totally actually available in your database. So you can
manage and you can see like video id. Like I have just created one
video so I can use the video one id video title
URL description status like it's in planning phase. You can see
actually there are different types of titles like planning, scripting,
recording, editing, even you can manage everything. Like it's a private
video, public video and unlisted video languages
you want to select, like you want to track. Like which videos have what kind
of subtitles. Definitely so there are a lot of like subtitles
out there and languages out there. Even you can edit new languages here and
same like which videos this come under? What kind of playlist?
Okay. And even you can create new playlist and videos like
you do. Definitely ask for edit new like end videos.
So there are two end videos. So you can add two and videos if you
want or nothing. Totally depend. And even like playlist is totally
depending on this site like you're planning or what.
So this is an amazing tool which is absolutely free of cost.
You can use it free of cost. You can download from my GitHub repository and
enjoy. Thank you,